Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004; 213494
  - Joshua Neustein, 1992-1993; cuid3132; 213604 (Box I:15, Folder 5)
  - Joshua Neustein -- Press Kit, 1992 August-November; cuid3133; 213603 (Box I:15, Folder 6)
  - Jane Gifford (Small Gallery), 1992-1993; cuid3134; 213602 (Box I:15, Folder 7)
  - Alan Michelson (Windows), 1993; cuid3135; 213601 (Box I:15, Folder 8)
  - NetherArt -- Biographies, Undated; cuid3136; 213600 (Box I:15, Folder 9)
  - NetherArt -- Correspondence, 1992 July-1993 September; cuid3137; 213599 (Box I:15, Folder 10)
  - NetherArt -- Exhibition, 1992-1993; cuid3138; 213598 (Box I:15, Folder 11)
  - NetherArt -- Public Relations, 1993 March-July; cuid3139; 213597 (Box I:15, Folder 12)
  - NetherArt -- Registration, 1990 November-1993 August; cuid3140; 213596 (Box I:15, Folder 13)
  - Other Borders -- Biographies, 1991-1993; cuid3141; 213595 (Box I:15, Folder 14)
  - Other Borders -- Correspondence, 1992 September-1993 May; cuid3142; 213594 (Box I:15, Folder 15)
  - Other Borders -- Exhibition, 1993; cuid3143; 213593 (Box I:15, Folder 16)
  - Other Borders -- Public Relations, 1991 May-1993 May; cuid3144; 213592 (Box I:15, Folder 17)
  - Other Borders -- Registration, 1993 February-1994 March; cuid3145; 213591 (Box I:15, Folder 18)
  - The Museum in the Gallery -- Exhibition, Circa 1993; cuid3146; 213590 (Box I:15, Folder 19)
  - The Museum in the Gallery -- Public Relations, 1993 May-July; cuid3147; 213589 (Box I:15, Folder 20)
  - Matthew Benedict (Windows), 1993 March-May; cuid3148; 213588 (Box I:15, Folder 21)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Biographies, 1992 October-November; cuid3149; 213587 (Box I:15, Folder 22)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992 February-1994 October; cuid3150; 213586 (Box I:15, Folder 23)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990-1994; cuid3151; 213585 (Box I:15, Folder 24)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Exhibition, 1993; cuid3152; 213584 (Box I:15, Folder 25)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Public Relations, 1993-1994; cuid3153; 213583 (Box I:15, Folder 26)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Registration, 1993 July-1994 November; cuid3154; 213582 (Box I:15, Folder 27)
  - Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), 1993; cuid3155; 213581 (Box I:15, File 28)
  - Jim Hodges (Windows), 1993-1995; cuid3156; 213580 (Box I:15, Folder 29)
  - Anyone in New York -- Biography, 1993 October; cuid3157; 213579 (Box I:15, Folder 30)
  - Anyone in New York -- Correspondence, 1993 May-December; cuid3158; 213578 (Box I:15, Folder 31)
  - Anyone in New York -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1993; cuid3159; 213577 (Box I:15, Folder 32)
  - Anyone in New York -- Public Relations, 1993 June-December; cuid3160; 213576 (Box I:15, Folder 33)
  - Brief Encounters (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1993 October-1994 January; cuid3161; 213575 (Box I:15, Folder 34)
  - Simon Patterson (Small Gallery), 1993 August-1994 April; cuid3162; 213574 (Box I:15, Folder 35)
  - Lydia Schouten (Windows), 1993 January-November; cuid3163; 213573 (Box I:15, Folder 36)
  - Art About Aids -- Biographies, 1989-Circa 1994; cuid3164; 213572 (Box I:15, Folder 37)
  - Art About Aids -- Correspondence, 1989 February-1993 December; cuid3165; 213571 (Box I:15, Folder 38)
  - Art About Aids -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994; cuid3166; 213570 (Box I:15, Folder 39)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (1 of 3), 1992 January-1994 July; cuid3167; 213569 (Box I:15, Folder 40)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (2 of 3), 1991 August-1994 February; cuid3168; 213568 (Box I:16, Folder 1)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (3 of 3), 1993 February-1994 April; cuid3169; 213567 (Box I:16, Folder 2)
  - Art About Aids -- Registration, 1991 March-1994 April; cuid3170; 213566 (Box I:16, Folder 3)
  - Visual Aids (Small Gallery), Circa 1993-1994; cuid3171; 213565 (Box I:16, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Stashkevetch (Windows), CIrca 1993-1994; cuid3172; 213564 (Box I:16, Folder 5)
  - Todd Watts -- Biographies, 1994; cuid3173; 213563 (Box I:16, Folder 6)
  - Todd Watts -- Correspondence, 1990 February-1994 June; cuid3174; 213562 (Box I:16, Folder 7)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibit Catalog, 1993-1994; cuid3175; 216171 (Box I:20, Folder 33)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994; cuid3176; 213561 (Box I:16, Folder 8)
  - Todd Watts -- Registration, 1993 December-1994 May; cuid3177; 213559 (Box I:16, Folder 10)
  - Three Women in Black (Windows), 1994; cuid3178; 213558 (Box I:16, Folder 11)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Correspondence, 1994 April-June; cuid3179; 213557 (Box I:16, Folder 12)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994; cuid3180; 213556 (Box I:16, Folder 13)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Public Relations, 1969 January-1994 July; cuid3181; 213555 (Box I:16, Folder 14)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Registration, 1994 February-August; cuid3182; 213554 (Box I:16, Folder 15)
  - Rob Wynne (Windows), 1993 October-1994 July; cuid3183; 213553 (Box I:16, Folder 16)
  - Arne Svenson (Small Gallery), 1994; cuid3184; 213552 (Box I:16, Folder 17)
  - Willie Doherty -- Biographies, 1992 November; cuid3185; 213551 (Box I:16, Folder 18)
  - Willie Doherty -- Correspondence, 1992 March-1994 August; cuid3186; 213550 (Box I:16, Folder 19)
  - Willie Doherty -- Public Relations, 1990 October-1994 October; cuid3187; 213549 (Box I:16, Folder 20)
  - Willie Doherty -- Registration, 1994 March-December; cuid3188; 213548 (Box I:16, Folder 21)
  - John Defazio (Small Gallery), 1993-1994; cuid3189; 213547 (Box I:16, Folder 22)
  - Rene Santos -- Biographies, 1994 September; cuid3190; 213546 (Box I:16, Folder 23)
  - Rene Santos -- Correspondence, 1982-1995 July; cuid3191; 213545 (Box I:16, Folder 24)
  - Rene Santos -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994; cuid3192; 213544 (Box I:16, Folder 25)
  - Rene Santos -- Public Relations, 1994-1995; cuid3193; 213543 (Box I:16, Folder 26)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Miscellaneous Correspondence, Checklists, 1 of 2), Circa 1994-1995; cuid3194; 213542 (Box I:16, Folder 27)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Miscellaneous Correspondence, Checklists, 2 of 2), 1994 August-October; cuid3195; 213541 (Box I:16, Folder 28)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Packing List, Condition), 1994 September-December; cuid3196; 213540 (Box I:16, Folder 29)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Biographies, 1992-1994; cuid3197; 213539 (Box I:16, Folder 30)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Correspondence, 1993 May-1995 February; cuid3198; 213538 (Box I:16, Folder 31)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Exhibition, 1994-Circa 1995; cuid3199; 213537 (Box I:16, Folder 32)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Public Relations, 1994 January-1995 February; cuid3200; 213536 (Box I:16, Folder 33)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Registration, 1994 July-1995 April; cuid3201; 213535 (Box I:16, Folder 34)
  - Jason Reed (Small Gallery and Windows), 1994 December-1995 February; cuid3202; 213534 (Box I:16, Folder 35)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Biographies, Undated; cuid3203; 213533 (Box I:16, Folder 36)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Correspondence, 1994 January-October; cuid3204; 213532 (Box I:16, Folder 37)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Exhibition, Circa 1994-1995; cuid3205; 213531 (Box I:16, Folder 38)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Public Relations, 1994-1995; cuid3206; 213530 (Box I:16, Folder 39)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Registration, 1995 March; cuid3207; 213529 (Box I:16, Folder 40)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Exhibition, 1995 March; cuid3208; 213528 (Box I:16, Folder 41)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Public Relations, 1995 April-May; cuid3209; 213527 (Box I:16, Folder 42)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1995 March; cuid3210; 213526 (Box I:16, Folder 43)
  - Ed McGowan (Windows), 1995; cuid3211; 213525 (Box I:16, Folder 44)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis), 1992-1995; cuid3212; 213524 (Box I:16, Folder 45)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Project Rembrandt, 1995; cuid3213; 213523 (Box I:16, Folder 46)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Biographies, 1981-1995; cuid3214; 213522 (Box I:17, Folder 1)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Entry Forms, Circa 1993-1995; cuid3215; 213521 (Box I:17, Folder 2)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Registration, 1995; cuid3216; 213520 (Box I:17, Folder 3)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), 1995-1996; cuid3217; 213519 (Box I:17, Folder 4)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Background Articles, Reviews, etc., 1992 March-Circa 1996; cuid3218; 213518 (Box I:17, Folder 5)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Catalogue Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1996; cuid3219; 213517 (Box I:17, Folder 6)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Catalogue Miscellaneous (2 of 2), Circa 1995-1997; cuid3220; 213516 (Box I:17, Folder 7)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Correspondence, 1995 September-1997 August; cuid3221; 213515 (Box I:17, Folder 8)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Development, 1995-1996; cuid3222; 213514 (Box I:17, Folder 9)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Exhibition Design, Circa 1994-1997; cuid3223; 213513 (Box I:17, Folder 10)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Exhibition List, 1995-1996; cuid3224; 213512 (Box I:17, Folder 11)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Installation, 1996-1997; cuid3225; 213511 (Box I:17, Folder 12)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1994-1996; cuid3226; 213510 (Box I:17, Folder 13)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1996; cuid3227; 213509 (Box I:17, Folder 14)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Press, 1996-1997; cuid3228; 213508 (Box I:17, Folder 15)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Registration, 1995 May-1997 January; cuid3229; 213507 (Box I:17, Folder 16)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Resumes, Undated; cuid3230; 213506 (Box I:17, Folder 17)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award, 1995 August-1996 April; cuid3231; 213505 (Box I:17, Folder 18)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (1 of 3), 1996 February-July; cuid3232; 213504 (Box I:17, Folder 19)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (2 of 3), Circa 1996; cuid3233; 213503 (Box I:17, Folder 20)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (3 of 3), 1996; cuid3234; 213502 (Box I:17, Folder 21)
  - Artists from Japan -- Artists Shown, 1996; cuid3235; 213501 (Box I:17, Folder 22)
  - Artists from Japan -- Condition Reports, 1996-1997; cuid3236; 213500 (Box I:17, Folder 23)
  - Artists from Japan -- Exhibition Signage, 1996; cuid3237; 213499 (Box I:17, Folder 24)
  - Artists from Japan -- Postponement, 1996; cuid3238; 213498 (Box I:17, Folder 25)
  - Artists from Japan -- Review, 1997 February 1; cuid3239; 213497 (Box I:17, Folder 26)
  - Artists from Japan -- Shipment and Installation, 1996 June-1997 February; cuid3240; 213496 (Box I:17, Folder 27)
  - Artists from Japan -- Shipment and Installation (Documents), 1996-1997; cuid3241; 213495 (Box I:17, Folder 28)
  - Walter Gaudnek Exhibit, 1994-1996; cuid3242; 216170 (Box I:20, Folder 34)
  - The Art of the Everyday: France in the '90s, 1993-1997; cuid3243 (Box I:21, Folder 1-54, Box I:22, Folder 1-52, Cassette 1, Box I:23, Folder 9-12, Box I:30, Folder 37-46, Box I:32, Folder 1-7)
  - The First Steps: Emerging Artists from Japan, 1997-2001; cuid3244 (Box I:22, Folder 53-56, Box I:23, Folder 1-8, Box I:26, Folder 1-21, Box I:30, Folder 25-34, Box I:31, Folder 46-52, Box I:32, Folder 11-24)
  - Langlands & Bell, 1991-1997; cuid3245 (Box I:23, Folder 13-28, Box I:30, Folder 35-36)
  - Nahum Zenil: Witness to the Self, 1997; cuid3246 (Box I:23, Folder 29-44)
  - Deep Storage: Arsenale der Erinnerung, 1997; cuid3247 (Box I:23, Folder 45-46)
  - War of Extermination: Wehrmacht Crimes between 1941-1944, 1997-1998; cuid3248 (Box I:23, Folder 47-55)
  - Desert Cliché: Israel Now - Local Images, 1996-1998; cuid3249 (Box I:23, Folder 56-67, Box I:24, Folder 1-4)
  - Shiro Kuramata: 1934-1991, 1997-1998; cuid3250 (Box I:24, Folder 5-60)
  - Police Pictures: The Photograph as Evidence, 1997-1998; cuid3251 (Box I:24, Folder 61-69, Box I:25, Folder 1-18)
  - Maya Lin: Topologies, 1996-1998; cuid3252 (Box I:25, Folder 19-44)
  - Counter Culture: Parisian Cabarets and the Avant-Garde, 1875-1905, 1996-1999; cuid3253 (Box I:25, Folder 45-70)
  - When Time Began to Rant and Rage: Figurative Painting from Twentieth-Century Ireland, 1998-2000; cuid3254 (Box I:26, Folder 22-61)
  - John Singer Sargent, Draughtsman: Works from the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999; cuid3255 (Box I:26, Folder 62-72)
  - Inverted Odysseys: Claude Cahun, Maya Deren, Cindy Sherman, 1998-2000; cuid3256 (Box I:27, Folder 1-92, Box I:28, Folder 1-11, Box I:30, Folder 1-6)
  - Sheer Realities: Clothing and Power in Nineteenth-Century Philippines, 1999-2000; cuid3257 (Box I:28, Folder 12-25)
  - Rudy Burckhardt and Friends: New York Artists of the 1950s and '60s, 2000-2003; cuid3258 (Box I:28, Folder 26-50, Box I:29, Folder 1-19)
  - Face to Face: Shiseido and the Manufacture of Beauty, 1900-2000, 1999-2000; cuid3259 (Box I:29, Folder 20-51, Box I:31, Folder 1-26)
  - Krizia: A Story, 1998-1999; cuid3260 (Box I:30, Folder 7-24)
  - Ben Shahn's New York: The Photography of Modern Times, 1999-2001; cuid3261 (Box I:31, Folder 27-45, Box I:32, Folder 8-10)
  - Dreams and Disillusion: Karel Teige and the Czech Avant-Garde, 2000-2001; cuid3262 (Box I:31, Folder 53-66, Box I:32, Folder 25-26)
  - Shifting Tides: Cuban Photography after the Revolution, 2000-2001; cuid3263 (Box I:32, Folder 27-28, Box I:33, Folder 1-17)
  - The Park Avenue Cubists: Gallatin, Morris, Frelinghuysen, and Shaw, 2000-2004; cuid3264 (Box I:32, Folder 29-44, Box I:35, Folder 42-79, Box I:36, Folder 1)
  - Pastoral to Post-Industrial: British Works on Paper from the Whitworth Art Gallery, 2001-2002; cuid3265 (Box I:33, Folder 18-37)
  - Seeing and Believing: The Art of Nancy Burson, 2000-2003; cuid3266 (Box I:33, Folder 38-61, Box I:34, Folder 1-11)
  - Priceless Children: American Photographs 1890-1925/ Child Labor and the Pictorialist Ideal, 2001-2002; cuid3267 (Box I:34, Folder 12-20)
  - Between Word and Image: Modern Iranian Visual Culture, 2001-2003; cuid3268 (Box I:34, Folder 21-60, Box I:35, Folder 1-41)
  - Park Avenue Cubists, 2001-2003; cuid3269 (Box 32)
  - Swiss Peaks, 2001-2003; cuid3270 (Box 32)
  - Swiss Peaks, 2001-2003; cuid3271 (Box 33)
  - Paul Kos, 2001-2003; cuid3272 (Box 33)
  - Diane Arbus, 2001-2004; cuid3273 (Box 33)
  - Erró, 2001-2004; cuid3274 (Box 33)
  - Erró, 2001-2004; cuid3275 (Box 34)
  - Atsuko Tanaka, 2001-2004; cuid3276 (Box 34)
  - Atsuko Tanaka, 2001-2004; cuid3277 (Box 35)
  - Mapping/Sitting, 2002-2005; cuid3278 (Box 35)
  - Ok/Okay, 2002-2005; cuid3279 (Box 36)
  - Paper Museums, 2002-2005; cuid3280 (Box 36)
  - The Downtown Show, 2003-2006; cuid3281 (Box 36)
  - The Downtown Show, 2003-2006; cuid3282 (Box 37)
  - Moving Pictures, 2004-2006; cuid3283 (Box 37)
  - Moving Pictures, 2004-2006; cuid3284 (Box 38)
  - Lee Mullican, 2004-2006; cuid3285 (Box 38)
  - The Downtown Show, 2004-2006; cuid3286 (Box 38)
  - The Downtown Show, 2004-2006; cuid3287 (Box 39)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1997-2007; cuid3288 (Box 39)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1997-2007; cuid3289 (Box 40)
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988; 212471
  This series contains administrative and development files, correspondence, WNYC recordings, and annual reports of New York University Art Collection and the Grey Art Gallery.
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1959-1977; 213473
    This subseries consists of letters of acknowledgement and other communications regarding donations to the New York University Art Collection and the Grey Art Gallery.
    - Chronological Miscellaneous Coorespondence, 1959-1969; 213493 (Box II:1, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Faculty Correspondence, 1961-1962; 213492 (Box II:1, Folder 2)
    - Chronological File -- February-July 1967, 1967 February-July; 213491 (Box II:1, Folder 3)
    - Chronological File -- August-December 1967, 1967 August-December; 213490 (Box II:1, Folder 4)
    - Chronological File -- January-June 1968, 1968 January-June; 213489 (Box II:1, Folder 5)
    - Chronological File -- July-December 1968, 1968 July-December; 213488 (Box II:1, Folder 6)
    - Chronological File -- 1969, 213487 (Box II:1, Folder 7)
    - Chronological File -- 1970, 213486 (Box II:1, Folder 8)
    - Chronological File -- 1971, 213485 (Box II:1, Folder 9)
    - Chronological File -- 1972, 213484 (Box II:1, Folder 10)
    - Chronological File -- 1973 (1 of 2), 213483 (Box II:1, Folder 11)
    - Chronological File -- 1973 (2 of 2), 213482 (Box II:1, Folder 12)
    - Chronological File -- 1974, 213481 (Box II:1, Folder 13)
    - Chronological File -- 1975 (1 of 2), 213480 (Box II:1, Folder 14)
    - Chronological File -- 1975 (2 of 2), 213479 (Box II:1, Folder 15)
    - Chronological File - JAS (1 of 2), 1976; 213478 (Box II:1, Folder 16)
    - Chronological File - JAS (2 of 2), 1976; 213477 (Box II:1, Folder 17)
    - Chronological File - JAS, 1976-1977; 213476 (Box II:1, Folder 18)
    - Thank You Letters -- 1967-1969, 213475 (Box II:1, Folder 19)
    - Thank You Letters -- 1969-1971, 213474 (Box II:1, Folder 20)
  - Subseries B: Grey, 1973-1980; 213468
    This subseries contains correspondence, memoranda, notes, newspaper clippings, printed materials and other miscellaneous materials relating to the foundation of the Grey Art Gallery and its involvement with Abby Grey.
    - Donor, 1973-1975; 213472 (Box II:1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1980 May; 213471 (Box II:1, Folder 22)
    - Honorary Dinner, 1979-1980; 213470 (Box II:1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence for Mrs. Abby, 1975-1979; 213469 (Box II:1, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: WNYC, 1968-1973; 213458
    This subseries contains audiovisual recordings of Ruth Bowman, the curator of the New York University Art Collection, related to her involvement in a television and radio series titled, "Views on Art." The subseries also includes correspondence, drafts, notes and printed materials.
    - Radio - "View on Art", 1972-1973; 213467 (Box II:1, Folder 25)
    - Radio - "View on Art", 1972-1973; 213466 (Box II:1, Folder 26)
    - TV - One to One (1 of 2), 1968-1972; 213465 (Box II:1, Folder 27)
    - TV - One to One (2 of 2), 1968-1972; 213464 (Box II:1, Folder 28)
    - TV, 1969-1970; 213463 (Box II:1, Folder 29)
    - TV, 1970-1971; 213462 (Box II:1, Folder 30)
    - TV, 1971-1972; 213461 (Box II:1, Folder 31)
    - TV (1 of 2), 1972-1973; 213460 (Box II:1, Folder 32)
    - TV (2 of 2), 1972-1973; 213459 (Box II:1, Folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-1980; 212472
    This subseries consists of applications, rejections and acceptances for the NEH, NEA and NYSCA grants; loan agreements, rejected loans, lender information and correspondence; insurance certificates, shipping, delivery and transportation receipts and paperwork; condition reports, appeals for funds, funding sources and resumes.
    - AFA Ancient Mexico Exhibit, 1964 November 3; 213457 (Box II:2, Folder 1)
    - Loan Return Forms -- New York Painter, 1967; 213456 (Box II:2, Folder 2)
    - Lenders, 1967 April-October; 213455 (Box II:2, Folder 3)
    - New York State Council on the Arts - Grant Application, 1970 June-August; 213454 (Box II:2, Folder 4)
    - 1971 Grant Application -- NYSCA, 213453 (Box II:2, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut, 1972 October 2; 213452 (Box II:2, Folder 6)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1972; 213451 (Box II:2, Folder 7)
    - Helena Rubenstein Foundation Grant, 1973-1974; 213450 (Box II:2, Folder 8)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1973-1975; 213449 (Box II:2, Folder 9)
    - Exhibitions Print Show - Hudson River Museum, 1973 January 13-March 4; 213448 (Box II:2, Folder 10)
    - Alan Sonfist - Rejected Exhibition Proposal, 1973 December-1975 December; 213447 (Box II:2, Folder 11)
    - Grant Proposals, 1974; 213446 (Box II:2, Folder 12)
    - NEH Grants Rejected -- Ashcan Painters, 1974; 213445 (Box II:2, Folder 13)
    - Draft Proposal -- NYSCA General Operations, 1974-1975; 213444 (Box II:2, Folder 14)
    - NEA Grant -- Prints and Techniques, 1975-1976; 213443 (Box II:2, Folder 15)
    - Prints and Technique Working File, 1976 March-April; 213442 (Box II:2, Folder 16)
    - NYSCA 2nd Proposal - Joy Gordon, 1975-1976; 213441 (Box II:2, Folder 17)
    - Loans -- Sara Roby Exhibition, 1976 January-March; 213440 (Box II:2, Folder 18)
    - Udine Receipts, 1976 July-August; 213439 (Box II:2, Folder 19)
    - NYSCA Program Proposal (1 of 2), 1976-1977; 213438 (Box II:2, Folder 20)
    - NYSCA Program Proposal (2 of 2), 1976-1977; 213437 (Box II:2, Folder 21)
    - Circa 1776 NEA Grant, 1976-1977; 213436 (Box II:2, Folder 22)
    - Circa 1776 Loans, 1976 June-October; 213435 (Box II:2, Folder 23)
    - 1776 Exhibition Loans, 1976 June-November; 213434 (Box II:2, Folder 24)
    - NYSCA Grant Preparatory Notes, circa 1976-1978; 213433 (Box II:2, Folder 25)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum Show, 1976 June-December; 213432 (Box II:2, Folder 26)
    - Tanavolil Shipping and Insurance, 1976 August-1977 January; 213431 (Box II:2, Folder 27)
    - Parviz Tanavoli Exhibition Billing, 1976 November 10-23; 213430 (Box II:2, Folder 28)
    - Beatrix Potter -- American Lenders Correspondence (1 of 2), 1976 November-1977 July; 213429 (Box II:2, Folder 29)
    - Beatrix Potter -- American Lenders Correspondence (2 of 2), 1976 November-1977 July; 213428 (Box II:2, Folder 30)
    - Beatrix Potter Correspondence to Armitt Trust, 1976 November-1978 January; 213427 (Box II:2, Folder 31)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (1 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November; 213426 (Box II:2, Folder 32)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (2 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November; 213425 (Box II:2, Folder 33)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (3 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November; 213424 (Box II:2, Folder 34)
    - Information on Lenders [Beatrix Potter] (1 of 2), 1977 February-May; 213423 (Box II:2, Folder 35)
    - Information on Lenders [Beatrix Potter] (2 of 2), 1977 February-May; 213422 (Box II:2, Folder 36)
    - Beatrix Potter Toronto-Boston Loans, 1977 April-June; 213421 (Box II:2, Folder 37)
    - Grants Pending/Accepted -- NEH Futurist Exhibition (1 of 2), 1977; 213420 (Box II:2, Folder 38)
    - Grants Pending/Accepted -- NEH Futurist Exhibition (2 of 2), 1977; 213419 (Box II:2, Folder 39)
    - Ree Morton Loans, 1977 May-August; 213418 (Box II:2, Folder 40)
    - Drawing and Collage Loans, 1977 May-October; 213417 (Box II:2, Folder 41)
    - Philadelphia Museum Correspondence - Gallery of Living Art Revisited, 1977-1978; 213416 (Box II:2, Folder 42)
    - Berkshire Museum Correspondence - "Gallery of Living Art", 1977-1978; 213415 (Box II:2, Folder 43)
    - Panoramic Photography, 1977-1979; 213414 (Box II:2, Folder 44)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders A-K, 1977 May-1978 January; 213413 (Box II:2, Folder 45)
    - History of Panoramic Photo - Insurance, 1977 May-September; 213412 (Box II:2, Folder 46)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders L, 1977 June-December; 213411 (Box II:2, Folder 47)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1977 June-December; 213410 (Box II:3, Folder 1)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1977 June-December; 213409 (Box II:3, Folder 2)
    - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman Loan Forms and Memos, 1977 January-1978 December 29; 213408 (Box II:3, Folder 3)
    - Wilmarth/Sandman Exhibition (Insurance and Transportation), 1977 November-1978 July; 213407 (Box II:3, Folder 4)
    - Wilmarth Black/White Photos, 1978 September-October; 213406 (Box II:3, Folder 5)
    - The Jewish Way of Death - NEH (Pending) (Rejected), 1978; 213405 (Box II:3, Folder 6)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Works in NY Show Only (1 of 2), 1978 May-December; 213404 (Box II:3, Folder 7)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Works in NY Show Only (2 of 2), 1978 May-December; 213403 (Box II:3, Folder 8)